inventorysource.com 2015-06-28

# Inventory Source Privacy Policy

##### Inventory Source Privacy Policy

**1\. PRIVACY STATEMENT**  
Inventory Source has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website www.inventorysource.com.

**2\. GATHERING OF SYSTEM INFORMATION**  
When you use Inventory Source’s services we track your activity on our website. Your personal information is used to identify you in our system allowing Inventory Source to charge for your use of subscribed Inventory Source services, and to contact you about the status of our service and any changes to our service via e-mail or telephone. We also use the information gathered from tracking user activities to improve our service. We also track your Internet Protocol (IP) address, domain name (if applicable), browser type, session duration, and transaction data-which is available to any site to which you connect. Inventory Source uses this information to administer the site and to further improve our service to you.

**3\. TRACKING OF COOKIES**  
A “cookie” is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies do not damage your computer. We use cookies to save your password so you don’t have to enter your password on every page.

**4\. CUSTOMER IDENTIFABLE INFORMATION**  
Our site’s registration form requires users to give us in depth contact information, this information is used to help us serve you better, it is never shared with third parties, except when you specifically authorize us. See section (5) below. Your contact information is also used to contact you, by our staff when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users’ qualifications for registration and to bill the user for products and services only and we do not share this information with our partners, unless you explicitly authorize us to.

**5\. FOREIGN SYSTEMS**  
This site contains links to other, non Inventory Source Partner sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Inventory Source will only transmit your information to Inventory Source partners when you have elected to sign up for a co-branded service that is linked with the Inventory Source system. For your convenience we will then transmit only the information required by the partner, through a secure channel to avoid you needing to re-enter the information. However it is your responsibility to ensure that you agree to the third parties privacy policy, and relevant licensing statements prior to authorizing us to transmit your information. For your convenience a link may be provided allowing you to review any privacy policies and licensing statements prior to data transmission.

**6\. INTERNAL USE OF INFORMATION**  
Our site provides a mechanism for people to send feedback and request more information. This information is not uniquely stored, but may be aggregated with other data to insure that we properly meet users’ expectations and have the necessary resources planned to accommodate future growth. A users’ contact information is also used to get in touch with the user when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to check our users’ qualifications and bill the user for products and services.

**7\. COPYRIGHT POLICY**  
Copyright. Without limiting any other remedies, Inventory Source may suspend or terminate your account if you are found to be infringing upon the copyright, trademark or other rights of third parties. Copyright, or Trademark owners can report infringing items, and have such items removed. Once the identity of a copyright or trademark owner is established, the owners may have limited access to some of your personally identifiable information as described in the Inventory Source Privacy Policy.

**8\. UPDATE POLICY**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Log in to account via http://www.InventorySource.com/ and upon entering registered email and password.

**9\. CONTACTING INVENTORY SOURCE**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Inventory Source  
60 Ocean Blvd,  
Atlantic Beach, FL, 32233  
support@www.inventorysource.com
